daytonainternationalspeedway.com 2011-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Daytona International Speedway

**We are always conscious and respectful of your personal privacy.**   
This Privacy Policy governs the use of the Daytona International Speedway, LLC (“DIS”) website (the “Site”).  The Privacy Policy’s purpose is to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and the way information is collected and used with respect to the Site. To make this notice easy to find, a link to this Privacy Policy is on the homepage of the Site.  This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect at the Sites, but does not apply to information collected through other means, including information provided by you in any non-Site ticket purchase (such as an in person purchase from the ticket office) at Daytona International Speedway. 

This Privacy Policy will answer your questions about the kind of information we collect and how we use it. If we change or update our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.  By using this Site, you acknowledge you have read this Privacy Policy and agree to the terms hereof. 

**  
What information do you gather and how do you use it?**   
DIS automatically collects certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Site, such as IP address, service provider, browser type, operating system, pages accessed on the Site and the date and time of access to optimize your user experience and enhance your time spent with us online. Each owner also receives information telling us what site from which you originated.

When you send DIS an e-mail, DIS will retain the content of the e-mail, your e-mail address, and our response in order to handle any follow-up questions you may have. DIS also uses this information to measure how effectively DIS addresses your concerns.

When purchasing tickets or merchandise, joining as a member, registering for promotions at the Site, or in connection with gifts, ecards, e-vites, forward-to-a-friend messages or any other messaging service, DIS may ask for your or your friend’s: 

  * Name 
  * E-mail address 
  * Credit card number and expiration date 
  * Billing address 
  * Shipping address 
  * Date of Birth 
  * Phone number

We use the personally identifiable information you choose to provide to DIS to process the transactions and services you request, to provide DIS and DIS affiliates promotional communications to you, to enable you to participate in sweepstakes and promotions, and to otherwise facilitate your use of the Site.

DIS may ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with us, and contact preferences.  This information may be combined with information about you, which DIS gathered from other offline sources. DIS and its affiliates use the information to design offers customized to your interests. For example, you may receive a special offer for your most frequently visited tracks. ****

**Information from other sources**   
DIS may receive information about you from other sources.  This may help improve the personalization of our service to you by providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you. ****

**  
Who do you share my personal information with?**   
DIS’ general policy is that DIS does not sell or share your name or other personally identifiable information to or with any non-affiliate third parties  for marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such sharing.  However, DIS may share your name and personally identifiable information with its affiliate companies for such affiliates to send you promotional communications such as emails, phone calls and newsletters.  DIS may share anonymous, aggregated information (information that does not individually identify a user) about all our users with third parties for any lawful purpose. ****

**Service providers**   
DIS may also share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, mailing house or web host) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.

**Protection of the Site and others**   
DIS may disclose information you provide at the Site when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Site, our users or other individuals. ****

**How does this Site use cookies and similar tracking technologies?**   
This Site uses cookies, tags, pixels and similar tracking technologies to allow DIS to recognize your preference information, keep track of your purchases, remember your Member Login and facilitate effective site administration. DIS uses the information we collect to enhance your visit to this site and provide you with information tailored to your needs.

You may elect to refuse cookies, but certain Site functions or access may not be available if you choose to do so. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies.

A Web beacon is an electronic image, also called a single-pixel or clear GIF, placed in the code of a webpage or in e-mails.  The Site uses Web beacons to track traffic patterns of users as they navigate from one page to another.  This information lets us tune and improve our users’ browsing experience.  As with cookies, the information that Web beacons collect is aggregated, anonymous “click stream” data, and is not associated with you as an individual.

We also use Web beacons through a third party website analytics provider, as well as standard Web server log files, to help us count visitors and evaluate the Site's technical capacity.  This information tells us how many people visit the Site, and helps us decide how to arrange pages in the most user-friendly way.  This also helps us keep the Site browser-friendly and more useful to our users.  We record information on Site traffic, but not on individual visitors to the Site, so no personal information about you will be kept or used. **

How does this Site comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act?

** The Website is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age.  DIS does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age, except for the limited circumstances described below.  In the event a child under the age of 13 submits a question to us on the Site and identifies his or her age, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit our use of the child’s email address for the sole purpose of responding to the child’s question on a one-time-only basis.  However, we will not use the child’s email address to re-contact the child and we will delete it from our records once we have responded.  If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. **

What choices do I have regarding

** **promotional communications?**  
DIS only sends promotional e-mail messages to you if you have voluntarily provided DIS with your e-mail address. Further, by providing your email address you agree that DIS may share such information with DIS affiliates and that such DIS affiliates may directly send you promotional materials.  You may request to be removed from this Site's e-mail subscription list by updating your personal account.  By clicking on the “Member Name” link at the top of the page you can access your personal account to make the necessary changes. You may also unsubscribe from any e-mail subscription by following the unsubscribe procedures set forth in each e-mail, including those received from DIS affiliates.     
 **

How do I update personal information such as my address?

**  
DIS asks that you keep your information as up-to-date as possible so you may get the maximum benefit from this Site. By clicking on the “Member Name” link at the top of the page you can access your personal account to make the necessary changes.    
**  
What about security at the Site?**  
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal privacy and data security laws and regulations to guard your personal information.  Unfortunately, no transmissions or data available through the Internet can be 100% secure and, accordingly, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any personal information or other information you provide to us.  DIS works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. DIS reveals only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, DIS transmits the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.  

 **What about links to and from other websites?**  
This Site may offer links to other websites, or you may have arrived at this Site from websites, that are operated by entities other than DIS.  These third party websites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these websites, or if you arrived from one of these websites, you should review the privacy policy of the website to understand how your personal information is collected, used, secured and disclosed. DIS is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third party websites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected, used or shared there. 

**Business transfers and bankruptcy**   
If some or all of the business assets of DIS or the Site are sold or transferred, your personal information, aggregated information, and any other information that we have collected in connection with the Site may be transferred as part of our business assets.  In such case, we also may retain a copy of this information.  Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered one of our assets and may be sold or transferred to third parties. 

**Community Feature**   
Any information, including Personal Information, that you contribute to a public area or feature of the Site, such as a user forum, blog, wiki or other open forum on the Site, will be made available to the general public.  Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive Personal Information to these public forums.  DIS is not responsible for the Personal Information or other information you choose to submit to these forums.   

**Third-party advertising  
** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**International Users**   
As this Site is operated from the United States and our computer systems are currently based in the United States, personal information submitted at the Site will be processed by DIS in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union.  By providing personal information at this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States. 

By using this Site, you signify your assent to the DIS Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the DIS Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. We reserve the right, at our complete discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. 

Effective Date:  March 1, 2010

Contact Information for DIS ****

Postal address:  
One Daytona Blvd.  
Daytona Beach, FL 32114  
Attention: Webmaster  
Telephone (386) 254-2700 ****
